Invention of Friends, I am Jignesh
Parmar, I welcome you all to my channel
CBS channel. Today in this video we are going to talk
about ICICI Prudential's Icc Purna Shyam Insurance Plan, which gives you
guaranteed benefits on maturity along with that.
So before moving ahead, as always, let
me tell you that it is
very important to watch this video till the end. If you
like this video, then like it, comment on it,
share it and if you have
not yet subscribed to this channel, then
subscribe quickly. This plan
is for conservative type of investors
who want savings and gangster returns, that too
with insurance. So let us get
information in very simple language about ICICI
Prudential Short Term Insurance Plan.
First of all, we will see
about its boundary conditions. So pay
attention to this table. The premium payment
is weak in this, but the PPT in this is
bullet of 15 years and one year policy
term. The PPT is of 65 years, in this there are 10 years and
15  The policy term is two years, so first let us
see it for five years, in that the 10 year power
system, the meaning of Indian
premium is 40 thousand 615 years, in
that William Hague 50,000 minimum and
maximum age of entry is 10 years,
in policy term the minimum set years and
maximum set salwar in 15 years, my mother
3 years and maximum 574, similarly the
age of maturity is 10 years, policy term
my age is 18 years, maximum centers and
in 15 years policy term the minimum is 18 years and
maximum is 72 years and there is premium payment of 1 year, in that there is
only one policy term
and that is 15 years, its medium Indian
premium is 50,000, minimum is 10 years and maximum is
357 years and maturity for me is
18 years and maximum is 72 years, in this the
premium is pre-board and really it means that
only animals can pack the premium,
all this is God, hey, the equivalent of book insurance
Importance of Indian Premier League
Instead of Jal premium you are going to pay
ten times more than that for switch on then this year
you will get it so friends this was the information
about Pandey conditions so now we will
see the current trend i.e.
according to the rate of return which is going on, we will see the illustration for both five years and five years in
that I have taken the example of the
policy term of 15 years only
so let's start this
first the PPT is 5 years and the policy
term is 15 years and here the premium is one
lakh rupees but friends this first column is
H after that is Iyer and its third
is maturity value friends if you
start a speed plan of 3 years and according to 5 years
you pay ₹5 in 5 years as per this calculation then at the
time of maturity i.e.
after 15 years you will get around
10 lakh 14 thousand 500 519 if we
start with parcel then the interest rate will be
10 lakh according to five point childhood  12
thousand ₹3 Similarly for 7 years 10 lakh 9 thousand
for 10 years at the rate of 5.5 per cent
10 lakh 5020 years this program was started
you will get an
interest rate of 5.40% and around 9 lakh 993336 rupees
for 25 years the interest rate is 5.35 for 30
years it is 5.30 for 40 years it is 5.20 for 50 years it
is 4.50 for 50 years and
3.75 for 57 years and there
you will get 8 lakh 7950 on maturity
friends this was the illustration 5 years
policy premium to pay for 5 years
and after 10 years i.e. in 15 years
you will get guaranteed income and how much will you get
we understood this now we will see the policy
premium term year and policy term example of 15 years
here also we
deposit one lakh rupees of premium every year i.e.
this year  If I deposit a premium of Rs 7 lakh,
how many
carrot fritters will I get after 15 years? So pay
attention to this channel, friends. If you start the three-year
recipe,
you will get around Rs 14 lakh with an interest rate of 5.85.
Similarly, for 10 years, you will get Rs 14 lakh, which is the
closest to Rs 571.
For 20 years, it is Rs 568, for 20 years it is Rs
558, for 40 years it is Rs 5.48, for 50 years it is Rs
1473. And in 57 years, you can get a 4
% return and you will get
Rs 11 lakh 28 thousand 126 after 15 years,
that too guaranteed. Friends, we have seen on this table that the
money has to be deposited this year and
according to the interest rate,
how much money will you get after 15 years. Friends, one
important thing is that this return
is absolutely guaranteed.
You will get as much as is written in the policy on maturity.
One more thing, there can be
changes in the quarter at any time.
Prudential
can make changes to it at any time, but
you will definitely get the same return as mentioned in the policy. Along with
this, you are getting
term insurance of 10 times the premium. So
friends, this plan
is very good for those investors who want to invest in a short term
with good insurance in an assured maturity
plan. Here,
on maturity, you will get an assured
return. If you look at the benefits of this plan, then
here you can avail tax benefit under ATC
and the return you get will be
tax free under the term and along with it there is a
guarantee of guaranteed return. You can take
this plan for your family and your children
and give them a
good insurance plan with
guaranteed maturity benefit. Friends, I
hope you liked this video.
You must have understood the information I have given through ICICI Prudential AMC. Show spot setting, first of all,
and if you have any doubt,
you can write to me in the comment box here.
Friends, I am Jagdish Sharma, I will leave now. See you.
In the next video
with another important information Jai Hind Jai
Bharat Aa Kar
Do
[Music]
Kar Do
Show More